Seino!
Galgal Channel GO!
Let's go today!
Girls Girls Girls and Lucky Lucky
We're going to have a joint field day!
I'm Misaki Tsuruya from the red group, and I'll be your host this time.
I'm Kira Yamaguchi from the white group.
Today, we've prepared 4 events that everyone can get excited about.
I've prepared 4 events that everyone can get excited about, so let's all do our best!
Let's all do our best!
Let's start with radio calisthenics.
Let's start with radio calisthenics!
Let's Dancing!
One, two, three, gah, start!
What did I say?
Left, right, feet up!
I'm sorry, my bucket...
Oh!
That's it!
Now, let's egonnolike it up in England with what we've got so far.
You're warming up!
Yes!
Perfect. Perfect.
How are you? Let's hear it.
Are you warm?
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
A little late.
Let's study the red group!
Hey!
I'm Hiira Kasahara.
I'm Minami Ishida.
I'm Kanna Sato
I am Momoka Sumiya
I am Akari Mori
I am Yoko Ogawa
I am Yuwa Higa
I am Misaki Tsuruya
Tension with everyone
Apple
Let's do our best!
Oh!
Let's play Tsuru-gumi!
I'm Yuzuha Oda, Cure White. I'm Yuzuha Oda, Cure White.
I'm Master Claire, who does her best in everything!
I'm Ririka Kamimura, the rabbit in charge of Welcome Home!
I'm Kiki and Kiki, the shating stars in your hearts!
I'm Mina Yamaguchi, who is in charge of your hearts and minds!
I'm cheerful and bright like the sun, the color of success arrangement!
This is Yuro Sugiura, the lucky lucky lady leader!
The yellow sun is shining brightly!
This is Haruta, who always curls her hair the way Naruto does!
Seino
Fluffy White
White team, let's do our best!
We will now begin the balance ball dodgeball.
I'm looking forward to it.
Nice to meet you!
Thank you very much!
Line show goods jacket pie!
Thank you for watching!
Ooh!
Oooh!
Go for it!
Come on!
Come on! Hey!
Oh!
That's good!
Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Aaah! Aaah!
Aaah!
Ahh!
Good night.
Big!
Come on!
Go, go, go, go!
Aaahhh!
Oh, hey,
Whoa!
Oh, there it is!
Here you go.
Whoaaaaah!
Please give it up. Please give it up.
Whoa!
Aaah!
Ugh!
Please give it up.
Oh no, oh no, oh no,
Please raise it.
Aah!
Yes, chick,
Here,
Yes, sir,
Oh-sen!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Thanks.
Yes, I'll do it.
TV Legend
AHHHH!
thanks for all your hard work!
X polished
X X So codon
Krakka
X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X
X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X XX ELEE
○ ○ ○ ○ Throwing out
○ ○ ○ ○
Congratulations!
Tires all over the place sideways
Back pair sideways
Back and forth sideways
Balance board sports are
Let's see.
Okay, that's enough.
Yes, done.
Okay, do it.
Yes, do it.
So, we have completed the first run of the field day project.
The score at this point is 100 points for red, and 80 points for white,
and 80 points for white.
I see.
But there will be more to come, and the final total will determine the winner,
I hope everyone is looking forward to it.
After the first game, I hadn't played badge ball for a long time, and it was a lot of fun,
I played it on Kiria's face,
It was you, wasn't it? It was you, wasn't it?
LOL!
Laughter.
It's a battle, you know, and it's getting hot.
It's nice. This is a field day.
This is a field day.
The second one is chasing balls and owner play.
It's not chasing.
Chasing.
Laughter.
Chasing ball drop.
In the second one, we're going to do the chasing ball game and the owner play,
See you all in the next video.
Enjoy the video.
Bye bye.
Well, we won the first game successfully, didn't we?
Yes, we did.
But, things calmed down a bit in the second round, and, well, it was more than White had already had.
Huh? Huh?
I'm talking out of my ass again, aren't I?
Why are you talking so much?
Well, I'll give you a start.
Now I'm making you stand up.
I'm giving him a chance to stand up.
It's the beginning, isn't it?
Oh no.
Kisei Sequence.
Like that.
I told him not to get carried away.
So I thought, let's just calm down a little bit.
I think I'm going to calm down a little bit more.
Next, are you going to play tama-no-tsuri?
I can't stay calm.
Yes, you're right.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'll calm down, but I'll be told.
I'm calm.
Let's walk like this.
They do ramen.
Ramen.
No, I have ramen here, too.
Ramen, ramen, ramen. Ramen, ramen, ramen because there are ramen.
Ramen, ramen.
Ramen.
No, Yoko is doing this.
From behind.
What's that ramen?
It's cheap.
I'm calm.
I'm not calm.
Huh?
Wasn't Hachimoki a little strange the other day?
No, the first one was the best.
It's like...from here on out.
It's fun.
I was pretty nervous at the beginning.
There was a lot of tension.
I was like, "Ahh," but then I thought, "I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it,
I'll do it, I'll do it,
He told me I could do better.
That part.
It was fun.
From the very first balance dodgeball, From the very first balance dodgeball,
I really, what can I say, raised my physical strength,
It was really tough from the beginning.
It was difficult to use a balance ball,
I was like, "Oh, yeah, I'm going to pop it.
But it was very easy to catch it.
It was fun.
Throwing is good, too,
We still have three more events to go,
Lucky, everyone, join forces,
Yes, sir.
It's only rivals, right?
That's right.
We will do our best together.
I will do my best.
Enjoy.
Bye-bye.